HIKARU (23)
HOSTESS
Ari.
ARI (29)
RAPPER/MODEL
Hmm…
It's sauna time.
What?
TAI-CHAN (22)
HAIRSTYLIST
I thought she'd go with Tai-chan.
BO (27)
COMMERCIAL PAINTER
She ended up choosing Ari.
MARIRIN (25)
BAR WORKER
Okay.
- Have fun.
- We'll be back.
I'll help you clear up these plates.
- Thanks.
- Yeah, this was good.
- We haven't really talked.
- Yeah.
The last time was when me and Taisei
were talking with you in the living room.
That's about it.
It's good to look each other in the eyes.
We can understand one another.
I agree.
Well, yeah, a lot's happened.
So I wanted to hear how you felt.
Honestly, I'm starting to hate myself
for being so cautious.
Yeah.
- I've been cheated on before…
- Mmm-hmm.
…so I tend to be cautious.
So when people are like,
"Just make up your mind
and choose already,"
honestly, that's been pretty hard
on me lately.
Mmm, I see.
I mean, what happened
with the omelet rice earlier…
was because Maririn said
she was interested in you.
She told us she wanted to write on yours.
And Ha-chan said
she wanted to write on Tai-chan's.
I wasn't sure of anything anymore.
So I told them, like, "Sure, go ahead."
Mmm.
If I gave it to one of you
when I haven't made up my mind,
that would be another mixed signal.
You know how people start liking someone
when they get jealous?
Oh.
I thought I could understand
my feelings better
if I made things more exciting,
so I thought yesterday
was both good and bad.
- Right.
- You were holding hands with her.
Uh, yeah.
Well, my feelings
were kind of all over the place that day.
At one moment, I was lost for words,
and she said something like,
"I can accept everything about you, Ari."
I said, "Thanks."
She was like, "You can hold my hands."
"Take your time and share with me
how you're feeling."
Can she really understand you, though?
Maybe she's just saying that.
- Are you having fun?
- No.
You're not?
- Do I look like I'm having fun?
- Yeah.
- Really?
- Are you bored?
No, I'm having fun.
- I've just been stressing over things.
- These past few days?
I've been stressing over things
so much that I'm almost hating myself.
Really.
I was in such a bad place.
Seriously.
I don't know if I can fall in love.
Talking to Maririn
made me realize some things.
Like, I can tell
she really came here to fall in love.
Mmm.
And I can see her being someone
who'd take time to support me.
We don't have
that many days left, you know?
Right. I don't want it to end
with, "Time's up."
So, for example, if you're still
equally interested in both me and Taisei,
or if you kind of like him more,
then I'd want to spend my time
with Maririn.
But if you're willing
to face up to me, then…
I am facing you,
but I'm not leaning either way right now.
There's a part of me
that's afraid of falling in love.
That feeling of becoming total strangers
after breaking up.
When I think about that, it really hurts.
Then don't break up.
Well, yeah, that's right.
There's no point
in thinking about breaking up.
Like, I'm thinking about marriage.
If you're thinking about the future,
you should definitely choose me.
I can make you happier than he can.
I don't know anymore.
You don't know either, do you?
I know.
- You do?
- I know.
I mean, instead of choosing
between me and Taisei here,
you should be comparing me
with all the guys across the country.
I'm willing to take on
anyone in that pool,
and I'm confident I can beat them.
So like, you don't have to be so confused.
- Leave it to me.
- But you're trying to confuse me.
That's right.
I don't know how I feel,
and that's exactly why, you know--
So, the goal for today is…
letting me hug you.
- You're too much.
- Hey, stand up for a sec.
- Oh, please.
- I wanna see how tall you are.
Just stand up for a sec.
I'm curious about the ceiling in here.
NAGANO
- I see what he did! It's the same trick!
- Oh, geez.
When Ari goes to the sauna,
he ends up hugging the girl.
- He does this with everyone.
- Seems like it.
- You're crushing me!
- How's that for ya?
- Mm.
- Sauna magic?
Wassup!
- Wassup?
- There she is.
- Sup, sup, sup!
- She's super hyped.
Pow, pow, pow! You know what it is.
Okay, so based on that vibe,
it must be a match with Ari?
Congrats.
- It felt way too good.
- Yeah.
That I was like…
…"I'm happy!"
- Like, the atmosphere…
- Yeah?
A YANKII DATING REALITY SHOW
WHERE LOVE LIVES ON THE EDGE
RAPPER FROM SAGAMIHARA
SPITTING LYRICS OF PURE LOVE
ARI
KAWASAKI'S IT-GIRL HOSTESS
OUT TO FIND A REAL MAN
HIKARU
KYOTO BAR OWNER
GOING ALL-IN FOR HIS WOMAN
NANIWA'S BARROOM BEAUTY
LOOKING FOR TRUE LOVE
MARIRIN
KURUME YANKII
WHO GREW UP BEHIND BARS
BO
EX-YAKUZA MMA FIGHTER
LOOKING FOR HIS RIDE-OR-DIE
MA-KUN
NAGOYA'S NO.1 HOSTESS
WHO PUTS MEN IN THEIR PLACE
ASSUN
FACE-TATTOOED STYLIST
WHO LOVES HARD
TAI-CHAN
AN HONEST MODEL
IN SEARCH OF LOVE
RURU
BRING ON THE FIGHTS
BRING ON THE LOVE
NO FILTER KICKBOXER
FROM MIYAGI
HA-CHAN
EX-NO.1 HOST
CHASING TRUE LOVE
KAZU-KUN
- Hey, hi.
- Morning.
I LOVE YOU
You're halfway through
your time at this school.
To help everyone get closer,
alcohol is allowed today.
- Thank you!
- That's great!
- I humbly accept.
- Let's do it! Let's toast first.
- Okay, let's toast.
- Cheers!
- What are you making?
- Infinite bell peppers.
What's "infinite bell peppers"?
Bell peppers you can eat endlessly.
- I'll help. Let's make it together.
- I'll get started.
Teach me
how to make infinite bell peppers.
I don't really know. I'm just saying it.
Kazu-kun doesn't seem very good
at being aggressive.
- Right.
- He hasn't had to be.
- Are we done bringing everything over?
- I think so.
- Let's go smoke.
- Okay.
I wish she'd ask me to do something.
It's pretty much always Leo.
I mean, I think I'm a pretty good catch.
I've got looks and money.
And I'm kind too.
But I'm really not the type
to initiate and be so aggressive.
Maybe this is the price for relying
on my looks and alcohol for so long.
My weapons are useless.
So he has a weakness.
- It's impressive he's that self-aware.
- It is impressive.
It's kind of admirable.
- Yoo-hoo.
- Hey there.
- Isn't it cold?
- It's cold.
Come here.
- It's cold. Put this on.
- What?
RURU (26)
MODEL
LEO (25)
BAR OWNER
- Thanks.
- Yep.
Right now, all we're experiencing
is what happens in this environment.
Yeah.
But once we're released
back into our real lives,
we'll be long-distance, right?
Yeah.
So I was thinking,
maybe we're being like this
only because of the environment
- we're in now.
- Yeah. I get that.
- So let's say we graduate.
- Yeah.
- Say I end up with you, and we graduate.
- Mmm.
And we go back to the real world.
Like, I ask myself, "Do I have
the resolve not to cheat on Leo?"
Mmm.
I really think cheating
is like some sort of sickness.
It's not a sickness.
- No. No.
- It can happen to anyone. For sure.
I don't know if that's something
I'll ever fix about myself.
What a confession!
I suppose if it ever does get fixed,
I'll be like "Wow, this is really love."
Mmm.
I know I won't chance it
when we're back in the world.
But as you know,
I have a history of cheating.
How can you trust me?
I wouldn't trust me. Never.
Because I already know
it's a sickness that can't be fixed.
- If anything, I'm glad you told me now.
- Mmm.
- But, but…
- Mmm?
It doesn't matter.
Don't worry. I'll straighten you out.
What, you think I won't?
- Straighten me out?
- I guarantee I will.
He told me he'd fix my cheating habit.
Like, yeah, no one's said that before.
Seriously, the things he says to me
are just so incredibly sincere.
Yeah, I'm really touched.
I mean, the things Leo says are just…
If we really do date…
I don't know how often it'll be,
but I kind of know he'll come see me.
I feel like he'd make me feel secure.
But my whole approach
to love is pretty distorted.
I don't know if I can be this open
when I face him.
I'm starting to feel scared
that I might hurt him.
Mmm.
I really wish I hadn't had
such a distorted mindset
in my past relationships.
I feel like,
if I'd been more genuine then,
I could've gone for Leo
without holding back.
But I've been way too distorted
when it comes to love.
You're taking forever over here.
What?
You're talking too long.
- Are we?
- You brought tequila?
Let's do this.
- What about our glasses?
- "Let's do this"? Right?
Just been you the whole time?
Yeah, we were just having
a deep conversation.
- And you just ruined it with the tequila.
- Mmm.
Thanks.
- See ya.
- Yeah.
Talk later.
He's nice enough to step aside.
All right.
I think I'm done drinking for tonight.
- He's a real man.
- Nice.
MAX MANLINESS
- So you just came to talk?
- That's right.
I think a transfer student
should definitely shake things up.
No, no, no, it's hard, though.
I know it's hard.
It would be hard for me too.
I mean, a lot of us already know
who we're into.
I mean, it's already bad.
- What is?
- Well, um…
- The other day, on Valentine's Day…
- Yeah?
…you told me to stay next to you.
- Mmm.
- But doesn't that go both ways?
I mean, if there's a girl
you even slightly want to talk to,
you can be more aggressive.
- I can't.
- Yes, you can.
I love my friends.
Okay.
Once I become friends with someone,
I can't help but back him up.
Yeah.
If it's between a girl and a guy,
I'd choose the guy.
- Yeah, right. I get that too.
- Yeah. That's why…
Right, that's why I said I didn't want
to make friends with them.
- I get that.
- Yeah.
- So, that hasn't really changed.
- Right.
What happens is,
I talk to them every day,
more than I do with the girls.
So I end up getting close to them.
- Yeah, you do.
- Yeah.
Like, if you were sitting next to Leo,
I couldn't just come in.
I see. Yeah, you can't do that
if you care about your friends.
He's a good guy.
He's actually a good guy.
He must've really pushed himself
at the beginning.
- He even got in a fight.
- Yeah.
Honestly, I cannot tell
how serious you are about me,
or if and how much
you like the other girls.
Shouldn't you try
to make me trust in you more?
Why are you being so passive in all this?
I'm not being passive,
I'm trying to look inside.
- Yeah.
- Really.
Listen, my exes were ugly as hell.
All of them.
Really, they were all so ugly,
everyone would agree.
- I feel bad for Leo.
- What? No, I didn't mean Leo.
- He's not my ex.
- No, no.
I'm just trying to say that
I'm the type who looks at what's inside.
- Oh, yeah.
- I mean, you're such a good-looking guy.
Anyone would agree
that you're a very good-looking guy.
I mean, we can all control
how we look on the outside.
I've had work done.
Anyone can change their looks.
Personality is what counts.
Man, Ruru is so cool.
Damn, these women
are gonna drive me crazy.
Come on, you're a transfer student.
- Try harder and show me how you feel!
- No, no, no.
Everyone's here to find love.
Guys and girls.
So when you say,
"You're the one who's not making a move,"
it kind of gets on my nerves.
Oh, but I'm leaning toward Leo right now.
That's what I'm telling you.
So if you have feelings for me,
it's for you to make a move on me.
- Don't you think?
- Okay, wait.
- Hold on. I get that.
- Yeah.
I never met a host I could trust.
I tend to go in
with a "you can't fool me" attitude.
I care about personality,
and I want someone
who comes at me straight
with their feelings.
I told Kazuma that he's good-looking,
but I'll judge him by his personality.
That was just some flexing.
On my part, that is.
With my actions and stuff.
Today kind of made me
make up my mind. Yeah.
I feel like…
like what I need is to be more aggressive.
It's all really offense from here.
If you won't sing, I'll make you sing…
Ruru bird.
What?
He's laughing out loud to himself.
You could tell he wasn't confident
from the "singing" line alone.
- For sure.
- Like, "What do I do?"
He was trying
to be careful with his words,
and the tension was rising.
That happens a lot to me as well.
Oh, me too.
I start to go, "Hahaha,"
and no one's laughing.
Is this lemon sour?
Yeah, sour lemon.
I'm having iichiko.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- So, what about you, Marina?
- What do you mean?
Seriously, I have no idea what's going on
with your love life around here.
Well, I have nothing.
Don't you have anyone
you're interested in?
Or anyone you think is nice?
I mean, everyone seems to be
in full-on happy mode,
and I feel like
I'm the only one who came here
to take this seriously or something.
- But that's fine, right? I mean…
- Yeah.
- Well…
- Yeah?
It's okay if you're into someone taken.
- The other guys are. Yeah.
- Well, yeah, that's true.
So…
Has anyone's face caught your eye?
- Their face?
- Their face, the way they talk and stuff?
Well, you look exactly like my ex.
Oh, wow. Oh, wow.
- Yeah, there are lots of guys,
- Yeah.
But the only one
who looks like my ex here is you.
- Oh, man.
- Don't be so awkward about it.
I can't say anything, 'cause I'm already…
- I only have eyes for Asuka.
- Yeah, I know.
I'm not an option for you.
Sorry about that.
I know.
BUDDHA LEAN
- Cheers.
I have something
I wanted to tell you today.
What is it?
I thought about it today,
and I still like you, Asuka.
I think you're pretty.
ASSUN (30)
ENTREPRENEUR/HOSTESS
That's all.
MA-KUN (28)
MMA FIGHTER
You're adorable.
That's all.
I was debating
with myself a bit yesterday.
Like, "What would happen to us
after our time here is over?"
Mmm.
Everyone's starting to worry about that.
It's like being under a spell.
Yeah, I definitely think that's how it is.
It's this environment.
I'm not planning
on leaving Gunma right away.
- Yeah.
- I don't think I can.
That said, if I'm going to think
about being with you,
there are things I'll have to change
somewhere along the line.
- Oh?
- Oh!
- Won't I?
- My heart skipped a beat.
Yeah, you're right.
- Hey!
- Not so fast.
We're saving ourselves.
- Listen.
- Hmm.
LOVEY-DOVEY
I mean, I know what you're like.
That's why I was so worried yesterday.
- Deep down, I'm a serious person.
- I know.
Yeah, I'm a straight shooter.
Exactly, it's your straight nature
that's making me debate with myself!
Understood.
No, I got it.
- I'm sorry.
- Yeah.
Man, that hurt.
What did?
- The kiss?
- Of course.
Kiss.
Ah.
I'm serious.
I'm really serious about you, Asuka.
No, I mean it.
- Bo.
- Hmm?
It's a good day. Another good day today.
How was it?
I asked for a kiss, and she kissed me.
He tells them everything.
Wait, so tell us more.
Was it the French kind?
- Yeah, it was French.
- You know what's next.
The D, man, the D.
The D, man. She wants the D.
- We're experienced men here.
- Oh, my God.
And the most advanced thing
that's happened is a kiss.
- I mean, isn't that crazy?
- Yeah.
And it's French too. Come on!
- No doubt.
- Hey, I gotta ask you.
- Were your eyes open or closed?
- Closed, okay.
- So lame. You gotta go like this.
- So lame.
- So adorable!
- They're so adorable.
- That's wassup.
- Don't say that.
It's like I'm under the magic
of Badly In Love. For real.
- The TV magic?
- Yeah, I'm under the TV magic.
I have a certain line I don't cross.
I was kinda like, "Kissing is a little…"
- That's a surprise.
- Really?
Apparently, I was drunk
and saying stuff like, "Let's kiss,"
but I'm not so sure.
I don't remember it.
- Oh, my.
- There it is.
Ichiro, the baseball player,
once said something I take to heart.
It's that people's judgment
tends to get worse at night.
Wait, Ichiro as in the Ichiro?
Yes, apparently
they're from the same hometown.
I'm still not really sure what to do.
I haven't fallen for him yet.
It takes time for me too.
What?
- Hey, wait.
- What?
- Plot twist.
- Huh?
So that wasn't the "I like you" kiss?
- But she clearly went for it.
- Yeah.
She tried it.
He would never think
she wouldn't remember this.
If they had listened to Mr. Ichiro
and taken their time,
if they kissed in the morning,
it's a different story.
Oh, right.
Mr. Ichiro never said anything
about kissing in the morning, okay?
He was talking
about mental attitude or something.
So now, we also have a love triangle
forming between Ruru, Leo, and Kazu-kun.
Ruru's great. She's so refreshing.
You could say she's leaving
all the options open on the table
- for Leo and Kazu-kun.
- Yeah.
She's basically saying,
"Here. Have all the information."
"So, if you want to do something,
go ahead."
True, she's being fair and transparent.
But isn't saying you'll cheat
pretty extreme by itself?
It's super extreme.
It really shows you how much resolve
she's coming here with.
- Yeah. I tell people everything.
- You do?
When I like someone,
I show all my cards right away.
Really?
So I really understand how Ruru feels.
But if you tell them that,
you risk not being chosen in the end,
and there's that chance
that you'll end up lonely
for the rest of your life.
Then why does she tell them?
Because he wants to be loved
for who she is.
Ah, I see.
I think that's the kind of bond
- she's craving deeply in a relationship.
- I see.
So Kazu-kun, Leo, and Ruru
are all starting to look like nice people.
- They're all nice.
- For sure.
They really are.
It's true.
Everyone in this love triangle is so nice.
- It's hard to pick sides.
- Tough choice.
They're so different from Hikaru's group.
Hikaru's group and Ruru's group.
- That's a mess.
- That's another story.
They're a total mess.
- Yeah.
- All of them.
Like, I want them to be happy,
but what can you do?
- Yeah, right?
- Yeah.
They should be a throuple.
- Right, that would be new.
- Right.
- And they can cheat all they want.
- A new shape of love.
- It'll be new.
- She can cheat.
You have free time this afternoon.
Is this prison?
- It's not prison.
- It is not prison.
If there is someone
you don't know very well yet,
or a person you're interested in,
get to know them better.
LOVE DINER
So…
- I was planning on telling you this today.
- Yeah?
I've been talking to mostly Ari so far,
but I figured he'd choose Hikaru.
But now I'm going back to the guy
I liked at the start.
- Yeah, yeah.
- To Tai-chan.
I'm gonna try talking to him some more.
- Oh, I see. Yeah, that's a good idea.
- Yeah, so…
I'm not sure if I actually like him,
but I think I'll try being
- a little more proactive in my own way.
- Oh, that's great to hear, Marina.
- Wait.
- Watch the knife.
- That's so great.
- Thanks.
Ohh!
Oh, it's great that she's moving on.
- Good luck.
- Yeah.
Really.
Oh. Hey.
You look shady. Yoo-hoo.
- How are you?
- I wonder how it's going.
- How it's going?
- How's it going for you?
- How are you? With Ari.
- You wanna talk about me?
Well, why not?
No, no, no. I don't know about him.
- Yeah.
- He's still going over to talk to Hikaru.
Yeah.
Right, you like her. You know.
Hmm…
- You're stressing over it too, huh?
- Well, of course.
I guess it's time to show my skills.
That's funny.
We haven't talked in this classroom
since that night.
So if this is the kind of guy you are,
none of us need you, okay?
There it is.
- I honestly think you're a piece of trash.
- Mmm.
Trash.
If you don't change,
if you can't act like a man,
then no one
is going to love you, Tai-chan.
Mmm-hmm.
That was scary.
I thought one of them was gonna stab me.
He's so gentle.
Tai-chan.
- But it went by so fast.
- Yeah.
Let's end this without any regrets.
- Yeah, you're right.
- Yeah.
- Too soon?
- No.
Oh, it's Ha-chan.
- Well, good luck.
- You too.
Hey.
- Was it too soon?
- No, not at all.
But it looks like you're really torn.
- Me?
- Yeah.
Of course I would be torn.
I can really tell.
Well, Hikaru seems really torn too.
- Hikaru?
- Yeah.
I see.
Anyway, I've been telling her about you
without hiding or anything.
Hmm?
I've told her how I'm feeling,
that I'm interested in you.
Oh, really?
But I don't want that to get in the way,
to keep Hikaru from going for you.
- Oh, okay.
- It's for you to decide.
It's not up to me.
You think it is? Really?
I had to muster up some courage
to say this.
- Really? You had to psyche up?
- Yeah. Yeah, I did.
I've never made the first move in my life.
- Oh, really?
- No, never.
- Should I raid their conversation?
- Go ahead.
- I'm going out.
- See ya.
Where's she going?
Ta-da!
Oh!
My first raid!
- What?
- Hey, can I talk to her?
- Just the two of us?
- Sure.
- Is that okay?
- Yeah.
Okay. You wanna sit here?
- Yeah, thanks.
- Okay, then.
- I wanted to have a chat with you.
- Okay.
Well, I thought about it a lot,
but I'm here to find love too, so…
Yeah.
I've been spending
most of my time with Leo.
Leo's been so focused on me,
so I felt I should do the same.
- Yeah.
- But our time here's limited.
- That's right.
- So I thought there might be
- someone here I could fall for.
- Yeah.
But maybe I just haven't had
the chance to talk to him yet.
Oh.
Yeah, and for me, that person was you.
We both live in Tokyo too.
- Oh. Seriously?
- Yeah. Yeah, so I came to talk to you now.
Thank you, thank you.
- I'm so happy. Honestly, thank you.
- Yeah.
I mean,
I didn't think I'd get to talk to you.
Right.
I mean, I was sure you and Leo,
you know, how you are,
you both seem so into each other.
Well, I think if I had
stronger feelings for Leo,
- I'd be more focused on him.
- Yeah.
And I probably wouldn't be talking
to anyone else.
- Yeah.
- But the thing with Leo…
the thing about dating him
in real life is the distance.
- Oh, since he's in Kyoto.
- He's in Kyoto, and I'm in Tokyo.
It'll be long-distance.
When we go back to reality,
there will be temptations,
and I can't say what will happen.
It's not like we live close enough
to just stay over at each other's places.
- That's true.
- Since we live in different cities.
So that's what's been holding me back
this whole time.
- Ah, so it's the distance?
- With Leo.
Yeah, the distance.
- I really look at people's personalities.
- Mmm.
Like how they act around others,
what kind of personality they have.
Isn't everything about me a negative?
- You don't think?
- But you've changed.
- You think so?
- You've changed.
If you hadn't, I wouldn't have come here.
I mean, I like guys who bring out
my maternal instincts.
Hmm.
When a strong man shows
a bit of his vulnerable side,
it brings out those maternal instincts,
and I feel like I need to help him,
or do something for him.
- I think that's love.
- Mmm.
Like, "Oh, Tai-chan
has this cute side to him."
Mmm.
I thought you were really adorable.
I don't feel that way about Leo.
- He's always like a real man.
- That's true.
He's always been straight with me.
He doesn't really lean on me,
- so that instinct doesn't come out.
- Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
But you do bring it out,
so I wanted to chat with you a bit.
Oh, really?
- Thanks.
- So talk to me.
- Okay.
- We haven't had a chance to get close
like Ma-kun and Assun are.
- Okay.
- So don't be shy and just talk to me.
- I'll talk to you too.
- My heart's still pounding.
- Why is it pounding?
- It's crazy. My heart's pounding.
- That's cute.
Things are starting to move.
It's finally happening.
I didn't think this could ever happen.
Her outfit today was insane.
Yeah, I was shocked.
It made my heart race.
- I feel like I'm starting to fall for her.
- Oh?
I'm falling for Ruru.
Remind yourself of that night, Tai-chan.
- She scolded you.
- If you date, that will be your life.
Hikaru.
Ruru.
I'm the youngest one here…
and it's time for me
to snatch them all up.
I guess my time has finally come.
Wait a second, who was Tai-chan into
at the beginning?
I think it was Ruru.
- It was Ruru?
- It was Ruru.
Tai-chan started liking Hikaru
after the letter mix-up.
- Right.
- Oh, right.
- He started liking her.
- I see.
So the first person Tai-chan went after
based on his own feelings
was Ruru.
- That's why you're here, Sensei.
- I'd forgotten about that.
- She's amazing.
- Sensei's memory is remarkable too.
- Yeah, it's great.
- And her analysis.
So when Lady Ruru raided…
Right.
She came to him, he suddenly remembered.
He never thought he'd get a chance.
And his crush came to see him herself.
Did you see that endorphin face he made
when she walked in?
Whoa.
So this is an endorphin face,
anatomically speaking.
Yes.
MEN
Maririn might be a bit of a femme fatale.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I think she is.
What?
- What? Maririn?
- Wait, Maririn isn't…
What?
She was like,
"You're just like my abusive ex."
"Your personality, your looks,
everything about you is exactly like him."
- Oh, really?
- I was like, "Wait, what?"
She only said it to me.
When we were alone.
She did say you're her type
and made a move on you.
Well, I like guys with scary faces,
and you're the only one who's a bit scary.
- I look the scariest?
- You kinda look scary.
I meant "scary" as a compliment.
Oh, but everyone always says
that I've got a scary face.
And she said
that Tai-chan's face is her type too.
You caught my attention first,
so I wrote you the letter--
Me? Not Leo?
- Huh? No.
- Didn't you say it was Leo?
- No, it was you.
- The guys were saying that.
I gave you the letter and wrote
that I was interested, right?
Oh.
- At the beginning.
- She did say that.
- That's right, she did, I almost forgot.
- Right.
Maririn was massaging Bo's shoulders
and hugged him in the picture.
I saw her do that too.
She's going after everyone.
Oh, wow, what are you doing?
Just imagine how she talks
when she's with the girls,
and how she talks
when she's alone with a guy.
She's totally different.
What's with the Maririn
character assassination all of a sudden?
She's being slandered.
These guys don't get it at all.
So, of all the guys,
who do you actually like the most, Marina?
Well, if we're talking about looks,
then Tai-chan's my favorite.
- Yeah, you said that.
- And I told Ari I think he's handsome.
- Mmm.
- I told Leo he's handsome too.
- And…
- Yeah.
- Earlier, Ma-kun told me…
He told me that you had said to him
that he was your type.
That's not what she said.
She didn't say that.
- Ma-kun is blowing it out of proportion.
- Yeah.
Wait, no, no.
What happened was,
I got asked who my type was.
- Then I told him, "You look like my ex."
- Yeah.
And he said, "But I like Assun."
I never meant it that way though.
I'm a nightlife worker,
so I tend to build people up when I talk.
- It's just a habit.
- Yeah.
And I ended up talking to him
that way too.
Mmm, mmm.
So, I'm sorry if I gave
you and Ma-kun the wrong idea.
But let me say…
You all told me that we're friends,
so I would never do anything
to betray you.
- I'll tell you before I do anything.
- Mmm.
But I think I definitely said it
the wrong way.
This one's on the guys, right?
The guys are at fault here.
- They painted her into someone she's not.
- They've been very unhelpful.
We get it,
we're not holding it against you.
- Neither is Assun.
- Yeah.
- I'm not blaming you at all.
- She wanted you to know what she heard.
- I thought I'd share it with you.
- Otherwise there'll be a misunderstanding.
I'm actually glad.
No one's ever been
this honest with me before.
Yeah.
It's like…
I thought I came here
just to learn about dating, but…
I got to know about friendship too.
- I just feel so grateful.
- Mmm.
- So I want you to trust me.
- Okay.
We really need to show Marina our love.
Right.
- It's more important than dating.
- Starting with the little acts of love.
Yeah, I really feel the same way.
It seems like with all the activities
we do, when she and I talk,
she always says
it's her first time doing it.
She really does.
She's said, "This is the first time
I've had a home-cooked meal like this."
Or, "This is the first time
I've done an activity like this."
You don't always meet people like her.
We've all been through
similar experiences,
but she's never had a home-cooked meal.
Marina is experiencing
a lot of things for the first time.
That says something.
I mean, I've been through
some pretty painful experiences myself,
but it made me realize she's had to carry…
…so much pain inside,
like, more than I've ever had to bear.
And that's why I believe in you, Marina.
Not just me.
Everyone else believes in you too.
Not a single one of us thinks
you'll betray us.
That's the first time anyone's said
something like that to me.
- Geez, that's another first time for you.
- No, I just meant…
- They're the nicest people.
- Come here, you!
- Take this!
- You guys are seriously the best.
I love you, damn it!
- Marina!
- I can't breathe.
I mean, people have told me I should die,
or that I shouldn't have been born.
I got to experience
the warmth of a home-cooked meal.
- I was so surprised.
- Yeah.
- I never knew people could be so warm.
I feel like you and I,
having gone through this stuff,
can support each other.
Thank you.
I never believed there could be
even one person who would like me.
- No, we all love you.
- We love you.
We really love you.
If anyone says they hate you,
I'll go beat them up for you right now.
- Yeah.
- That's how much we care about you.
I couldn't care less about guys right now.
We'll go and tell them
to shut the hell up.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Right now.
They really don't get it.
Man, I'm really pissed off right now.
LADIES
- It was like this from the start.
- I remember the first incident.
- Go, girls!
- It's always been these three.
BRING ON LIFE
- Oh, what's this?
- Are they confronting them?
She's stretching and getting ready.
- Vroom.
- Oh, this is a setup.
Whoa. This is kinda scary.
What kind of kinky play is this?
It's intimidating.
The reason we called you guys
in here today is…
Well, it's because we heard you boys
are having some doubts about Marina now.
So I'll let Marina
explain her side to you.
Yeah, so first of all,
I wanted to say that
it took a little while to open up
to you guys about my feelings.
And I finally felt ready
to explore relationships with everyone.
So I really wanted to talk to each of you,
one by one, and get closer to you.
But I work serving customers,
so I give compliments
without really thinking about it.
I don't mean to give the wrong idea,
but I do that kind of stuff all the time.
And…
I just heard you were all kind of
complaining about it behind my back.
Marina came here to find romance, right?
So when she's alone with someone,
she says things like,
"You're cool," or "You're handsome,"
or, "I want to talk to you more."
She says these things
based on her first impression.
But when you guys say stuff like,
"She's always trying to please everyone,"
- we think that's pretty damn pathetic.
- Exactly.
- The Minister has spoken.
- She's so tough!
But this opinion of you makes sense
when you approach multiple guys
at the same time, don't you think?
- So what should I do?
- Isn't that the game?
She came here to find love, it makes sense
she'd approach different people.
She explained it, we get it.
Maybe instead of you guys
whining to each other about it,
if you had something to say to Marina,
you could've just told her face-to-face.
She said that
because she wants to get close to you.
- Mmm.
- So we're being delusional idiots?
- That's right.
- I see.
If you guys just talk
among yourselves and don't include us,
you won't know our side of the story.
Is what I said so wrong?
I've always worked in nightlife,
I mean, maybe it's just habit
that makes me say that stuff.
But still…
I'm saying it
because I want to get closer to everyone.
But you guys talk about it
like I'm trying to mess things up.
That was never my intention.
I'm not this crazy girl or anything.
Sure, it took me a while to open up,
but I want to face this seriously.
Face it with each of you,
like I said before.
But you even think that's wrong.
It's just my habit, I guess,
to try to please people.
Sorry for crying.
I know it's a little intense.
Mmm. No, it's okay.
- It's hard for me to understand.
- Me too.
You said Leo
was who you were most interested in.
You told him in the sauna.
- No. I did say you were handsome.
- You said I was handsome.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Anyone can say someone is handsome.
- Well, yeah, but--
- I said it to Ari too… Not today.
- Yesterday, in the sauna.
- Yeah. I told him he was handsome.
We're just saying
it's not fair for everyone
to label Maririn as some crazy girl
- because of that.
- Yeah.
If I can't say things like that,
how do I talk?
Like saying, "You have nice skin."
I have a habit of complimenting people.
I don't know what to say.
I'll say this, please get to know me
because that's what I want.
It makes me think
you're all a bunch of virgins.
Seriously, everyone says things
like "you're cool" all the time.
We'd say it to anyone
if we think they're cool.
"Virgins"?
We're saying,
if you're gonna go back there
and pick apart what you think you heard,
just stop, 'cause it's pathetic.
Well, yeah, I admit it was wrong of us
to keep going on about you
without letting you clear the air,
and I'm sorry about that.
But I still think it's risky
to use that as a way
to get close to someone right off the bat.
Are you saying
I have to change everything?
- Isn't that too hard?
- It is hard.
And it's not even wrong.
I just wouldn't do it.
I'm a transfer student, so this isn't
as big for me as the other guys,
but you've all been doing this
with six guys and five girls
for a while now.
Of course we hang on every word you say.
Telling someone they're handsome here
is different from the outside world.
We're here to find love.
We only have a limited number of people,
so don't you think it's natural for us
to wonder what a compliment means?
It's the environment.
All she did was try to show affection,
or get closer to everyone.
If that's how it is,
we won't feel anything
from what Maririn says anymore.
How are we supposed to feel
when you say these things?
Like, "You guys must be virgins,"
or "You make no sense," right?
This is the environment.
We don't have much time,
all we have is what you say.
When we listen
to every single word we hear,
you tell us, "No, that's not right."
It makes us unable
to say or feel anything.
Couldn't you just say, "I want to get
to know you better, so let's talk"?
Are the compliments necessary?
I just compliment people like that.
Maybe you stop doing that from now on?
I'm sorry,
but that might be really hard for me.
This is what I've always done.
It's a standoff
between the guys and the girls.
So you're just saying I'm crazy.
- No one's saying that.
- That's not it.
- We never said that.
No, it's not like I'm being negative.
She's trying to do something about it.
- Mmm.
- You should understand that.
Is it that funny?
Let's focus on moving forward.
I'm stepping out.
This is bad.
So this is Badly In Love.
I don't think anyone's in love.
The guys and the girls
are in different camps.
- It's crazy.
- We're taking a break from love.
How is this possible?
It's already Episode 6.
What's the big deal anyway?
I'd love to hear a compliment.
- You'd like that, you mean?
- Maririn can tell me I'm cool.
Right, exactly.
But they're complaining she said it
to everyone? That's not very manly.
Exactly.
It isn't very manly at all.
- I wish I could talk to them.
- Oh, absolutely.